{
	"item": [{
		"question": "It is used to specify how websites/documents are displayed/presented. (Answer in abbreviated form)",
		"answer": "CSS"
	}, {
		"question": "Fill in the blank to apply white text color to the paragraph. p { ____#FFF; }",
		"answer": "color:"
	}, {
		"question": "Turn the text into a comment: __This is a comment__",
		"answer": "<--This is a comment-->"
	}, {
		"question": "How do you select the first-child of p?",
		"answer": "p:first-child"
	}, {
		"question": "CSS code for setting the font-size to 50px",
		"answer": "font-size: 50px;"
	}, {
		"question": "Match all i elements in all first child p elements",
		"answer": "i:firstchild {}"
	}, {
		"question": "He proposed the CSS",
		"answer": "Hakon Wium Lee "
	}, {
		"question": "At-Rule used for defining font-styles which are typically Google Fonts",
		"answer": "@font-face"
	}, {
		"question": "It has the highest precedence among all other precedence factors",
		"answer": "Important Declarations"
	}, {
		"question": "Allows authors to specify the values of several properties with a single property.",
		"answer": "Shorthand properties"
	}, {
		"question": "CSS uses ___________ to extend the code within a block of CSS code.",
		"answer": "@extend"
	}, {
		"question": "It provides functionality without having to write CSS.",
		"answer": "CSS Frameworks"
	}, {
		"question": "It allows users/developers to make use of the features of the browsers.",
		"answer": "Polyfills"
	}, {
		"question": "CSS uses _________ to include the mixins within the CSS code.",
		"answer": "@include"
	}, {
		"question": "Accepts parameters which can then be used to set the values of the attributes.",
		"answer": "Mixins"
	}]
}